



Specialties

- > UI/UX Design
- > Visual Design
- > Interaction Design
- > Prototyping
- > Project Management
- > Story Boarding
- > Graphic Design
- > SVG Icons
- > Illustration
- > Typography

F Tools

- > Figma, Sketch & Axure
- > Adobe Creative Suite
- > Affinity Creative Suite
- > HTML
- > CSS, SASS, Flexbox, Grid
- JavaScript
- > Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Gridsome
- > Bootstrap
- > Git
- > Agile, Lean

Experience

- > UI/UX Designer/Visual Designer, Zander Insurance Full-Time, Nashville, TN, 08/2021-present
- > 2017 present

Contracting, <u>ValentinaDesign.com</u>, <u>DrewHarper.com</u>, <u>Dollar General mockup</u>, continuous learning: Nashville Software Scool, JavaScript, Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Gridsome.

> UI/UX Designer, TN Dept of Education

Contract, Nashville, TN, 12/2016 – 06/2017

> UI/UX Designer, Civic Inc.

Contract, Nashville, TN, 09/2013 - 02/2015

> UI/UX Designer, JPay.com

Full-time, Miami, FL, 2008 - 2013

- > <u>JPay.com</u>, Mobile, One-man UX Design/Marketing Dept.
- > UI/UX Designer, Safari Ltd.

Contract, Miami, FL, 2007-2008

> UI/UX Designer, Planning Grp Int. – now Sapient Nitro

Contract, Miami, FL, 2006

> UI/UX Designer, Diaz & Cooper Adv.

Full-time, Miami, FL, 2003 - 2006

> Art Director & Web Designer, TBWA

Full-time, London UK, 1998 - 2000

Profile

Art Director in Miami. Moved to London, England and worked at top ten Ad agency TBWA (Omnicom). Early 2000s moved to UI/UX Design.

When UX design is good it seems simple and inevitable. Love reducing UX complexity to UX delight. Also highly productive; you need 7 versions for meeting tomorrow? No problem. Like my Bézier curves perfect.

Highly proficient with Adobe CS, including InDesign, Sketch, Figma, Axure, Bootstrap. Loving new into Affinity Creative Suite tools.

Education

- > International Fine Arts College, 1987, Miami, FL, Commercial Art, AA Degree
- > Trent College, 1984, Long Eaton, UK Boarding school in England, received Art Scholarship. Played Rugby for my county.

Referrals

- Don Pham, Project Manager don.kim.pham@gmail.com (954) 801-9975
- > Mike Mack, Coder mikemack88@gmail.com (415) 509-1909
- > Joanna Perry, Creative Director joanna@nomadhome.net +44 788-418-7100